SHEILA BANICE KABIRO PHONE: +254 795 811 714

EMAIL: sheilabernicew@gmail.com

PERSONAL DATA

ID NO: 35537066
DATE OF BIRTH: 26/03/1998
NATIONALITY: Kenyan
SEX: Female

LANGUAGES: Kiswahili, English

RELIGION: Christian

ABOUT ME

Client-focused software developer, with experience in mobile application and web development. Adept at managing all stages of the software development life-cycle from gathering requirements to deployment and maintenance.

Proficient with object-oriented programming languages and data structures.

CAREER HISTORY

WEB DEVELOPER

June 2020 to September 2020

Utheri Farmers Sacco

Key Responsibilities:

- I was responsible for their digital signage and creation of social media accounts
- I designed the Sacco's Website http://utherisacco.com/

MOBILE DEVELOPER

October 2020 to January 2021

Alfones Communication

Key Responsibilities:

- I was responsible for rebuilding an their previous mobile application system and adding more features in it
- I was responsible for fixing all system bugs

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages: Java, SQL, Javascript, HTML5, CSS

Framework/ Platforms: NodeJS, AngularJS, Jquery, Bootstrap

Environments: Linux, Windows

Database Management Systems: SQL Server, SQLite, SQL

EDUCATION & TRAINING

Software Development Certification, Moringa School, Nairobi	2019
Diploma in Accounting, Rware College of Accounts, Nyeri	2016-2018
KCSE certificate, Moi Equator Girls School, Nanyuki	2012-2015
KCPE certificate, Kiera Academy , Meru South	2000-2011

PASTIMES AND ACTIVITIES

- During my free time I work on some of my personal projects. You can find them on my github page https://github.com/Shyla27
- Besides code I enjoy taking nature photography. And writing Poetry
- I'm also keen in reading IT blog & Medium DURING my free time to get what's new in the IT world and learn something new

REFERENCES:

Name : Fredrick Njagi Muriithi Job Title : Chairman Utheri Sacco

Phone No : 0724 463537